Tufts University Gallery Records UA108
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, circa 1996 -- 2012; UA108.002; 4.8 Linear Feet
  - Branded and On Display Spring, 2008; UA108.002.042.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Ivan Navarro Spring, 2008; UA108.002.042.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Skinner and Cook Bequest Show, Spring, 2008; UA108.002.042.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Production-Mwangi Traveling Cross-Currents, Spring, 2008; UA108.002.042.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Contrapuntal Lines-Matar and Milhem Fall, 2008; UA108.002.042.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Do-Hosuh: Paratrooper II Fall, 2008; UA108.002.042.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Stack of papers: Kabakov/"Center of Cosmic Energy", circa 2008; UA108.002.042.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - PINARDI, circa 2008; UA108.002.042.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Sixth Annual Juried Summer Exhibition Summer, 2008 -- 2009; UA108.002.042.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Exhibition: Rosamond Purcell: Two Rooms Photographs, circa 2008; UA108.002.042.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Imagenes e Historias: Chicana Altar-Inspired Art, circa 2008; UA108.002.042.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Hiroshi Sugimoto Fall, 1996; UA108.002.043.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Christo+Jeanne-Claude (Fall), 1998; UA108.002.043.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Christo+Jeanne Claude Press, circa 1998; UA108.002.043.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Looking Forward, Looking Black (Fall), 2000; UA108.002.043.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Mark Shetabi, 2001; UA108.002.043.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Munro Text Materials (Spring), 2002; UA108.002.043.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Munro Misc (Spring), 2002; UA108.002.043.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Abayudaya-Misc (Spring), 2003; UA108.002.043.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Common Ground (Fall), 2003; UA108.002.043.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Iranian-American Artists (Fall), 2004; UA108.002.043.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Niki St. Phalle (Fall), 2004; UA108.002.043.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Marisol (March), 2005; UA108.002.043.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Museum Studies (Spring), 2005; UA108.002.043.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Mei Linghom (Fall), 2005; UA108.002.043.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Bocas del "Ceniza" (Spring), 2006; UA108.002.043.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Empire Checklist Working Docs, 2007; UA108.002.043.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Kamrooz Aram-Empire, 2007; UA108.002.043.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Z. Bouabdella-Empire, 2007; UA108.002.043.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Burtynsky (Spring), 2007; UA108.002.043.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Yang (Spring), 2007; UA108.002.043.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Global Village Shelters (Fall), 2007; UA108.002.043.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Distribution Agreement-Distributed Art Publishers (September), 2007; UA108.002.043.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Remis Doho Paratrooper (Winter), 2007; UA108.002.043.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA Thesis Exhibition Loan Agreements (December), 2007; UA108.002.043.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA, 2007 -- 2008; UA108.002.043.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Branded and On Display (February), 2008; UA108.002.043.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Navarro, Ivan (Spring), 2008; UA108.002.043.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Dinh Q Le-Tapestry of Memories (Spring), 2008; UA108.002.043.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Ivan Navarro (Spring), 2008; UA108.002.043.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Branded and On Display (Spring), 2008; UA108.002.043.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - "Branded"-Krannert (J. Fox) (Spring), 2008; UA108.002.043.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Koppelman (Fall), 2008; UA108.002.043.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Palestinians Loan Letters (Fall), 2008; UA108.002.043.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Bohtaina Abe Milhem (Fall), 2008; UA108.002.043.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Empire Loan Letters and Insurance (Summer), 2008; UA108.002.043.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Brian Knep (April), 2009; UA108.002.043.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Original Dinh Q Le Loan Forms (April), 2009; UA108.002.043.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Remis-convergence (April), 2009; UA108.002.043.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - C. Tomaszewski (Spring), 2009; UA108.002.043.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Tomaszewski (Spring), 2009; UA108.002.043.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Dinh Q Le (Spring), 2009; UA108.002.043.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Summer, 2009; UA108.002.043.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Sacred Monsters (Fall), 2009; UA108.002.043.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Brian Knep (Fall), 2009; UA108.002.043.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA Thesis (April), 2009 -- 2010; UA108.002.043.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - New Media Wall-Justin Cooper, 2010; UA108.002.043.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Mexico- Reproductive Rights (May), 2010; UA108.002.043.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA Thesis (May), 2009 -- 2010; UA108.002.043.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA Thesis (December), 2009 -- 2010; UA108.002.043.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Koppelman Spring - Saya Woolfalk, 2010; UA108.002.043.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Mexico Beyond its Revolution (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Harvard Loans-Mexico (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Mexico Beyond its Revolution (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Zavala Loans (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Schneider Enriquez Loan (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Boston Public Library Loans (Spring), 2010; UA108.002.043.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - IGL Spring Exhibition, 2010; UA108.002.043.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Interface (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Renovating Walden (Fall), 2010; UA108.002.043.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - SMFA Exhibition (December), 2010; UA108.002.043.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Museum Studies, 2010; UA108.002.043.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Terry Rosenberg-Remis NMW (Spring), 2011; UA108.002.043.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - U.Arts Contract-Pop Women Spring, 2011; UA108.002.043.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Pop Women Checklist Spring, 2011; UA108.002.043.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Pop Women Spring, 2011; UA108.002.043.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Pop Women Brooklyn Agreement Spring, 2011; UA108.002.043.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - MFA Exhibition April, 2011; UA108.002.043.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - SMFA Exhibition May, 2011; UA108.002.043.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Museum Studies Exhibition May, 2011; UA108.002.043.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Summer, 2011; UA108.002.043.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Dorothy Grebenak, circa 2011; UA108.002.043.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - T. Silverstein: Independent Contractor, circa 2011; UA108.002.043.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
  - Kabakov Gobo CD, circa 2011; UA108.002.043.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43)
- 2019 accessions, 2017 -- 2019; UA108.000372; 389 Megabytes 191 files
  This series contains materials relating to the Alumnae Murals, including copies of archival source materials, a bibliography and readings, images of the murals, object file information about the murals, the object file itself, and copies of presentations given during a forum on December 20, 2017. This accession also includes two WARC files created by the Digital Archivist using WebRecorder to capture a 360 degree video of the murals created by the Art Gallery, and a website on the murals.
  Materials were compiled and files created between 2017 and 2019. Files include scans and copies of materials created earlier, including archival materials held by Digital Collections and Archives in UA021, Facilities Management Records.
  Existence and Location of Originals
  Materials in the "Archival Scans" folder were copied from Facilities Management Records, 1849-2004. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
  This series is open for research.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Items in the "Web Crawls" folder must be viewed using Web Recorder. A Box Note with instructions on how to download and use Web Recorder can be found in the same folder.
  Transferred by Dina Deitsch, 2019, accession UA-2019-026.
  Murals --Alumnae Lounge
  - Alumnae Lounge Murals records, 2017 -- 2019; UA108.000373; 389 Megabytes 191 files